公路在哪里
Where's the road?
你居然还活着
You're...freakin' alive.
到底发生了什么
What the hell happened?
迪克爆炸时我们站得太近了
Standing too close to exploding Dick
被炸进了炼狱
sends your ass straight to purgatory.
你一直在炼狱
You were in purgatory?
你怎么逃出来的
Well, how'd you get out?
怎么  救你一命都不说句谢谢
What? No thanks for saving you, ha?
我有你想要的东西
I got something you need.
-什么东西  -离开的方法
- Yeah, what's that? - A way out.
你有什么好处
What's in it for you?
搭个顺风车
I'm hopping a ride.
我们成功了  兄弟  我真不敢相信
We made it, brother. I can't believe it.
我也不敢相信
You and me both.
那小卡呢  他也在那里吗
What about Cass? Was he there?
小卡没能逃出来
Yeah, Cass didn't make it.
小卡  我想我们还是
Cass, I think we better g--
小卡
Cass?
那小卡死了  你亲眼看见了吗
So Cass is dead? You saw him die?
我看得够多了
I saw enough.
我才不想做什么先知
I don't want to be a prophet.
保护他是我们的责任
He was our responsibility.
你却连电话也不接
And you couldn't answer the damn phone.
那我们去找他
Let's find him.
地狱之王刚扭断了我女朋友的脖子
The king of hell just snapped my girlfriend's neck.
克劳力抓走了你  我看到了
Crowley kidnapped you. I saw that.
你说你逃出去了
Saying you escaped.
怎么逃的
How?
那里有块碑
There was a tablet.
还有一块碑
There's another tablet?
这块碑有名字吗
Did this tablet have a name?
"恶魔"
"Demons."
恶魔怎么了
What about demons?
驱逐地球上的所有恶魔
Banish all demons off the face of the earth.
把他们永远关起来
Lock them away forever.
如今
伊利诺伊州  芝加哥
抱歉让您久等了  维利先生
So sorry to have kept you waiting, Mr. Vili.
只是  您很久没跟我们联系了
It's just...it's been so long since you checked in with us.
我们在档案馆找了半天
We had to dig through our archives.
没关系  亲爱的
Don't worry about me, dear.
我有的是时间
I've got plenty of time.
您说是哪个箱子来着
Which box is it again?
一号
One.
抱歉
I'm...sorry.
您是说第一号箱子吗
Did you say one, as in box number one?
如果没记错的话
If memory serves.
我们上次翻修的时候
During our last renovation,
把原先的保险箱都换了
we had to replace the safe boxes,
您的保险箱就放在新保险箱中
and we put yours inside a new one.
抱歉  先生  那是根骨头吗
I'm...sorry, sir, but...is that a bone?
可不是根普通的骨头  亲爱的
Not just any bone, my dear.
这是根无比珍贵的骨头
An extremely valuable one.
那...很高兴这些年来我们能为您安全保管
Well, I'm happy we were able to keep it safe for you all these years.
今天还有什么需要我帮忙的吗
Is there anything else I can help you with today?
哦对  说起来
Why, yes, now that I think about it.
我想要"提款"
I'd like to make a withdrawal.
《凶鬼恶灵》  第八季  第二集
虎 妈 你 好
你开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me?
你肯定是开玩笑
You're kidding me.
怎么了
What?
我想顺道看望我妈这个要求过分吗
Is it too much to ask if we can swing by and check on my mom?
"顺道"
"Swing by"?
需要朝相反的方向开一天的车
It's a day's drive in the opposite direction.
你知道吧
You know that, right?
是  我知道我们赶时间
Yes. I understand we're in a hurry.
是啊  那你干什么还要问
Okay, well, then, what's the problem?
想想钱宁被拧断的脖子
Channing's broken neck is my problem!
我不想见到我妈被拧成螺旋状
As in I'd rather not see my mom twisted into a corkscrew.
-这孩子说的对  迪恩  -你别管
- Kid's got a point, Dean. - Stay out of this.
凯文  你妈妈好着呢
Kevin, your mom is fine.
你怎么知道
How can you possibly know that?
因为克劳力需要她好好活着
Because Crowley needs her to be, okay?
现在他很可能让一群保镖守着她的房子
In fact, he's probably got the place stacked with bodyguards right now,
保护着她  这样你一出现
protecting her so that when you do show up,
就能把你俩一起抓住
they'll pounce on you both.
你说这话是想安慰我吗
Is that supposed to make me feel better?
她是个诱饵  老弟  就这么简单
She's bait, man, plain and simple.
你想主动奔过去咬钩吗
And you want to swim right up and bite the hook?
听着  我们能制住克劳利
Look, we have got Crowley by the short and curlies, okay?
只要找到那块石碑  喊出咒语
All we need to do is find the tablet, whip up the spell,
嘭  从此天下太平
and -- boom! -- sunshine and sandy beaches.
迪恩  我妈妈孤身一人
Dean, my mom's all alone.
被恶魔们包围着
She's surrounded by demons.
你真的无法理解我想去看望她的心情吗
Can you really not understand why I want to make sure she's okay?
该死
Son of a bitch.
好啊  咱们走
Fine. Let's go.
密歇根  内博市
虎妈  九点方向
Tiger mom, 9:00.
哪里
Where?
左窗
Left window.
她看起来没事
She seems okay.
很难过  但是没事
Sad...but okay.
看看那个邮差
Check out the mailman.
那是卡尔
Yeah, that's Carl.
怎么了
So what?
好吧  就我们停下来这会儿
Yeah, well, Carl's filled your mom's mailbox
卡尔往你妈妈邮箱里塞了三次信了
three times since we've been sitting here.
他是恶魔
He's a demon?
看到那个园丁没
And see the gardener?
你觉得那些植物还没浇够水吗
Think that plant needs any more water?
他会回来的  你要坚信这一点
He'll be back. You just have to believe.
谢谢你  尤尼斯
Thanks, Eunis.
我坚信这一点
And I do believe.
我只是  希望我能做点什么
I just... wish I could do more.
琳达  你能做的只有待在家里
Linda, you're doing all you should by staying here.
他得知道自己有家可归
He needs to know he has a home to come back to.
你好  妈妈
Hi, mom.
凯  凯文
Kev-- Kevin!
这是
What...
她没问题
She's clean.
你闻到了吗
Do you smell that?
[咒语]
Et secta diabolica, omnis congregatio, omnis legio,
Omnis incursio infernalis adversarii,
[咒语]
Omnis spiritus exorcizamus!
尤尼斯
Eunis!
那不是尤尼斯
That's not Eunis.
谭太太  您的朋友被恶魔附体了
Mrs. Tran, your friend was possessed by a demon.
你看过《驱魔人》吗
Have you ever seen "The exorcist"?
你这一年就去干这个了吗
Is that what you've been doing all year --
看电视
Watching television?
你非得杀死她吗
Did you really have to kill her?
不杀她  恶魔会向克劳力通报凯文的下落
The demon would have warned Crowley where Kevin was if we didn't.
克劳力就是绑架你的那个人吗
And Crowley is the one who kidnapped you?
是  他需要我替他翻译一块破石碑
Yeah. He needs me to translate his stupid tablet
这样他就能一统宇宙
so he can take over the universe or something.
所以我们得拿到石碑
Which is why we need to get it
关上地狱之门  把克劳力永远关在里面
so that we can slam the gates of hell forever with Crowley inside.
这样以后就不会发生这种惨剧了
So that things like that don't ever happen again.
上帝的先知  是吧
Prophet of the lord, huh?
名号不错
It does have a nice ring to it.
我去收拾东西
I'll get packed.
克劳力去过那个小木屋了
We're gonna need a safe house
我们得再找个藏身地  那么...
since Crowley's been to the cabin, so --
藏身地
Safe house?
咱们不是要去拿石碑吗
I thought we were going to get the tablet.
是我们几个
Uh, we are.
你得去一个没有恶魔的地方
You're taking a trip to a demon-free zone.
不顾凯文可能再次落到这个克劳力手上吗
And risk letting Kevin fall into the hands of this Crowley again?
办不到
I don't think so.
谭太太  很抱歉  迪恩说的对
Ms. Tran, all due respect, Dean's right.
克劳力可不仅仅是个杀手
Crowley -- he's not just a killer.
折磨人是他的拿手好戏
He trades in torment.
如果他找到办法把你的灵魂从身体剥离
And if he can find a way to separate your soul from you,
他就会把你的灵魂带去地狱
he'll take that soul to hell and --
然后把你的灵魂烧成渣渣
and roast it till there's nothing left but black smoke.
你还是让我们来处理吧
Look, it's best if you let us handle this.
我明白
I understand.
但我不担心自己的灵魂
But it's not my soul I'm worried about.
我只担心我儿子的
It's my son's.
凯文  你不来帮我们一把吗
Kevin, you want to back us up here?
咱们大老远来就是把她从火坑里拉出来
Came all the way down here to pull her out of the fire.
她现在却想着跳回去
Now she wants to jump right back in.
你觉得我能指挥得动她吗
Like I can tell her what to do?
好吧  跟我们一起去是有条件的
All right. Coming with us has conditions --
用魔法袋躲开恶魔
Uh, hex bags to stay off the bad guys' radar
还得帮你纹个符
and, uh, you're gonna have to get inked up.
你说什么
Do what, now?
是
Yeah, uh...
还有你  游击手
...you, too, shortstop.
能避免恶魔附体
Keeps the demons out.
好啊
Fine.
真的
Really?
你以为这是我第一次纹身吗
What, like it's my first tattoo?
你闻到了吗  小萨姆
You smell it, Sammy?
烧焦的肉
Burning flesh?
复仇  不远了
Revenge. So close.
喂  你是怎么反驱魔的
Hey, how'd you do that reverse-exorcism thing?
倒着念咒语
Just said the verse backwards.
怀俄明州  拉勒米
就目前来看  这儿没问题
So, place is clean, far as I can tell.
很好  祝我们成功
All right. Positive thoughts.
你居然把神之语藏在尿布袋里
You hid the word of god in a diaper bag?
没有
No.
闭嘴
Shut up.
这些柜子净给我们惹麻烦
Got nothing but trouble with these lockers.
有段时间天天被撬
Got broke into damn near every day for a while.
一直不知道是谁  直到昨天
Could never figure out who it was till yesterday.
-那你们知道谁干的  -当然
- Oh, so you know who did it? - Sure.
克莱姆・斯梅德利  我接替的他
Was Clem Smedley, a guy who worked the desk before me.
求你告诉我他已经被捕了
Please tell me he's down at county right now.
是  就等着传讯呢
Yep, waiting for arraignment.
多谢
Thanks.
早该猜到他们会在一个包里放寻回器
Should have known they'd plant a lojack in one of them bags.
那个杰里挺不错
Sharp guy, that Jerry.
接替我正合适
He'll be a fine replacement for me.
好吧
Right.
其中有个柜子里放着一块石碑
Well, in one of those lockers, there was a tablet.
你知道去哪儿了吗
Do you know where it is?
我的律师不在场  我能承认这个吗
Can I even acknowledge that without my lawyer here?
听我说  如果你能合作
Uh, look, I'm sure we can work out a little, uh,
我们就能和当地警方商量商量
something-something with the locals if you just cooperate.
商量什么
What kind of something-something?
我觉得他不知道  老兄
I don't think he knows, man.
宽大处理
Leniency?
他肯定知道
Oh, he knows.
天使在哪里
Where's the angel?
我是这么想的
So, here's what I'm thinking --
免除一切指控
Full immunity from all charges,
包括过去  现在和未来的
both past, present, and future.
迪恩  别这样
Dean. Come on.
感觉到了吗
You feel that?
有条小溪
There's a stream.
说下去
Go on.
流经一片空地  离这里不远
It runs through a clearing not far from here.
我带你们去
I'll show you.
告诉我就行了
How about you just tell me?
迪恩
Dean!
第一大街和主街交汇处的当铺
Pawn shop, first and main.
继续说
Go on.
三天的路程
Three days' journey.
沿着溪流走
Follow the stream.
会出现一片空地
There's a clearing.
你的天使就在那儿
You'll find your angel there.
小杂种  你知道吗
You know what, mutt?
我相信你
I believe you.
迪恩
Dean?
我们走
Come on.
你好  先生
Hello, sir.
尼尔和赛克探员  联调局
Agents Neil and Sixx, FBI.
我们在寻找一块石碑
Uh, we're looking for a tablet.
大概有这么大  上面刻着些象形文字
About, uh, yea big, got some hieroglyphic crap on it.
是一个叫克莱姆的贼卖给你的
Sold to you by a thief named Clem.
-有印象吗  -没有
- Ring a bell? - Nope.
莱尔  我今天过得很不顺
Hey, Lyle, I've had a really, really bad day today,
所以我没心情和你磨蹭
so I'm not in the mood to dillydally.
如果你想来硬的  我很乐意成全你
If you want to do this the rough way, I am happy to oblige.
好啊
Sure.
如果你们想出名的话  那就来硬的
We can do it that way, if you want to get famous.
外面的车是你的吗
Is that your car outside?
关你什么事  贱货
What's it to you, mail-order?
伙计
Hey, pal!
没事
I got it.
我注意到你的车牌照已经过期了
I notice you're driving with expired tags,
也许是因为车是你从谁那儿买的
maybe because you just acquired it in a trade,
那样的话  你应该还没去登记
and I'm guessing that means you haven't registered it yet,
那你也肯定还没交税
which means you haven't paid the tax.
我说的对吧
Is that correct?
不关你的事
None of your business.
凯文  商品价格参考手册
Kevin, average blue book
法拉利F430蜘蛛平均标价是多少
on a 2010 Ferrari F430 spider?
二十一万七千美元
$217,000.
乘以百分之五的怀俄明州税呢
And the 5% Wyoming tax?
一万八百五十美元
$10,850.
一万美元
$10,000.
直觉告诉我
Something tells me
这么大笔税款  你肯定想逃掉
you're the type who might balk at a tax bill that big.
你们干什么  联调局查税吗
W-what is this, an FBI audit?
不是  但是我哥哥
No. But my brother,
碰巧在怀俄明州估税员办公室工作
who happens to work for the Wyoming tax assessor's office
如果他觉得这里有人逃税
could arrange that if he thought something
倒是可以来查税
untoward was happening here.
你想要哪个
So what's it going to be?
石碑还是那辆欧洲产的垃圾跑车
The tablet or that piece of Eurotrash crap you call a car?
你确定就是这儿
Sure this is the right place?
当铺那家伙说的就是这儿
It's what the pawn slip says.
凯文
Kevin?
你是谁
Who wants to know?
别激动  迪恩  我不会偷走你的先知的
Oh, relax, Dean. I'm not going to steal your prophet.
你一定就是凯文的母亲
Ah. And you must be Kevin's mother.
女士  这真是我的荣幸
Beau, and it is my absolute pleasure.
凯文
And, um, Kevin.
我真是幸运
Imagine my luck.
我一直苦苦寻找你
Here I was, working so hard looking for you
却从没想过也许你也在找我
that I never stopped to think you might be looking for me.
我有东西给你
I have something for you.
什么东西
What is it?
一场独家拍卖会的邀请函  亲爱的
An invitation, dear man, to a very exclusive auction.
凯文
我猜猜  你们要卖那块石碑  对吗
Let me guess, where you'll be selling the tablet.
得到像神之语这么烫手的山芋
Well, when we acquire an item as hot as the word of God,
明智之举当然是尽快转手
it's smart to unload it as fast as possible.
而且我们也急需一位
And we are in such desperate need
今晚盛会的头牌人物
of a headliner for tonight's gala.
我希望你还有三张你那个拍卖会的门票
Well, I hope you have three extra tickets to your little ebay party,
因为先知要和我们在一起
cause the prophet's with us.
如果你担心先知的人身安全
Oh, if you're worried about the safety of the prophet,
请放心  我们有  "禁止打架  念咒
rest assured that we have a strict "No casting, no cursing,
为了好玩用超自然力量
no supernaturally flicking the two of you against the wall
把你俩扔到墙上"的规定
just for the fun of it " policy.
是吗  你怎么管住竞拍者
Is that right? How'd you manage that?
我毕竟是一位神o的得力助手
Well, I am the right hand of a God, after all.
准确的说  是普路托斯[财神]
Plutus, specifically.
那都不是行星了
Is that even a planet anymore?
迪恩跟冥王星搞混了
是贪婪之神
It's the God of greed.
而且我的神保卫拍卖堂
And my liege has warded these premises
不受来自地狱  天堂等等的干扰
against hell, heaven, and beyond...
对某些竞拍者来说还挺重要的
Quite necessary with some of the players we see.
巧的是
And incidentally,
对你的宝贝先知  也极可能是最安全的地方
quite possibly the safest place your precious prophet could be.
既然时间宝贵
Mm. Well, since time is of the essence,
我就直接在先知的邀请函上
perhaps I'll just go ahead and add a plus-three
多加三个名额好了
to the prophet's invitation.
好吗
Copacetic?
谢谢你  花生先生
Well, thank you, Mr. Peanut!
好吧
All right.
我们有多少钱参与竞拍
What do we have to bid?
我们总不能空着手去吧
What? We can't just show up there empty-handed.
迪恩  我们名下只有几张伪造的金卡
Dean, all we have to our names is a few hacked gold cards.
好吧  我们得想想奇招了
All right. Well, then, we're gonna have to get creative.
不行
No. Mnh-mnh.
你说出来我就杀了你
Say it and I will kill you,
你的孩子  还有孙子
your children, and your grandchildren.
好吧
Okay, okay. Uh...
等一下
Wait a second.
这些拍卖会  他们事先会向竞拍者
These...these auctions, they display the items
展示要拍卖的东西  对吧
to the bidders beforehand, right?
是啊  然后呢
Yeah, so?
那我们只要
So all we got to do
让凯文靠近  然后记住咒语就行了
is get Kevin close enough to memorize the spell.
你觉得呢  天才
What do you think, brainiac?
你觉得你能背住吗
Think you can swing it?
他当然可以背住
Of course he can swing it...
绝对没有问题
If the bumper stickers on my previa mean anything.
他们只是开玩笑  宝贝
They didn't mean it, baby.
你好  迪恩
Now, now, Dean.
只有大家都合作  系统才能良好运作
The system only works when everyone participates.
我会回来拿的
I'll be back for this.
我们怎么知道他们都是谁
How the hell are we supposed to know who's who?
这太简单了  迪恩  他们都是怪物
It's pretty simple, Dean. They're all monsters.
看这儿
Hey, hey.
好极了
Great.
跟我们预计的不太一样
I guess we're not as original as we thought.
没关系  我们想个备用计划就好了
It's okay. It's okay. We just got to come up with a plan "B."
那第一计划是什么呢
And what, pray tell, could possibly have been plan "A"?
把先知带到世界上最危险的地方
Bring the prophet to the most dangerous place on earth,
让他记住石碑上的内容再溜掉吗
memorize the tablet, and then va-moose?
你好  孩子们
Hello, boys.
克劳力
Crowley.
凯文  见到你很高兴
Kevin. What a pleasure to see you.
你女朋友的事我很抱歉
Sorry about your little playdate.
叫什么来着
Her name?
不过  有时候做事呢
Well, if you're gonna make an omelet,
免不了要有些牺牲
sometimes you have to break some spines.
这位可爱的女士是谁
And who is this lovely young thing?
肯定是你姐姐
Must be your sister.
离我儿子远一点
Stay away from my son.
真棒
Charming.
我现在最想做的事  就是搂着她尸体睡觉
Defiling her corpse has just made number one on my to-do list.
别为了小事大动干戈
Don't mind a little love tap,
动作再大一点
but anything more,
恐怕那边的朋友就会请你们出去了
and our mookie pals here may just throw you out,
那就太可惜了
and that would be a shame.
他说的没错  迪恩  忍一忍
He's right, Dean. It's not worth it.
还是小的说话入耳
Listen to moose, squirrel.
主人来了
Ah. Here comes our host.
尊贵的来宾  敬请入座
Honored guests, please take your seats.
那就是普路托斯吗
That's Plutus?
他算什么  糖果店的神吗
What is he, god of the candy aisle?
先生们  拍卖会开始了
Gentlemen, the auction is starting.
竞拍顺利
Good luck with the bidding.
那拳打的漂亮
Nice right hook.
迪恩・温彻斯特
Dean Winchester?
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
不  但是我认识卡西迪奥
Uh, no, but, uh, I knew Castiel.
你是天使吗
You're an angel?
这人是我临时就近找的皮囊
This -- this was the nearest vessel on short notice.
我们一般不找这类型的  不过
We don't usually come to things like this, but, uh...
你们为石碑而来吗
You're chasing the magic rock?
我们负责保护神之语
We protect the word of God.
到目前为止干得漂亮啊  阿尔菲
Well, awesome job so far, uh...Alfie.
我真名叫萨曼德里奥
Actually, my name is Samandriel.
还是阿尔菲顺口
Let's just stick with Alfie.
我想问你卡西迪奥的情况
I wanted to ask you about Castiel.
他怎么样了
What happened to him?
我和小卡  杀死了迪克・罗曼
Well, me and Cass -- we, uh -- we iced Dick Roman
结果就搭上了去炼狱的单程火箭
and got a one-way rocket ride to purgatory for our trouble.
但你逃出来了  那他呢
But you escaped. Did -- did Castiel?
天堂里至今仍有些天使坚信
You know, there are some in heaven who still believe,
尽管他犯下那么多错
despite his mistakes,
卡西迪奥一直都只想做好事
that Castiel's heart was always in the right place.
你也是这类人吗
Are you one of them?
我觉得他的问题就是心肠太好
I think too much heart was always Castiel's problem.
小卡
Cass!
迪恩
Dean.
小卡
Cass?
见到你真好
Damn, it's good to see you.
-绒毛胡子挺不错  -谢谢
- Nice peach fuzz. - Thank you.
给你介绍个朋友  这位是本尼
You should meet somebody. This is Benny.
本尼  这位是小卡
Benny, this is Cass.
你好
Hola.
你们怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
杀出来的
The bloody way.
你还好吗
You feeling okay?
你是说我还疯着吗
You mean am I still...
非要这么说的话  是的
Yeah, if you want to be on the nose about it, sure.
我这回全好了
No. I'm perfectly sane.
不过94%的疯子都说自己是正常人
But, then, 94% of psychotics think they're perfectly sane,
那不如问问我们自己  什么才算正常
so I guess we'd have to ask ourselves, "What is sane?"
这是个好问题
That's a good question.
-你为什么背叛了迪恩  -别这么说
- Why'd you bail on Dean? - Dude.
我听说  你们是一起来到这里
The way I hear it, you two hit monster land,
而你自己走了
and hot wings here took off.
我觉得他该跟你解释一下
I figure he owes you some backstory.
我们当时被包围了
Look, we were surrounded, okay?
肯定有什么怪物袭击了小卡
Some freak jumped Cass.
然后他打败了他们  对吗
Obviously, he kicked its ass, right?
不
No.
什么
What?
我跑掉了
I ran away.
你跑掉了
You ran away?
我没有办法
I had to.
这就是你把我丢给狼群的借口吗
That's your excuse for leaving me with those gorilla-wolves?
-迪恩  -你跑了  然后呢  去露营了吗
- Dean.  - You bailed out and, what, went camping?
我每天晚上向你祈祷
I prayed to you, Cass, every night.
-我知道  -你知道还...
- I know. - You know and you didn't...
你哪根筋不对了
What the hell's wrong with you?
我是个身在堕落之地的天使
I am an angel in a land of abominations.
很多怪物从我们一到这里就盯上了我
There have been things hunting me from the moment we arrived.
我也是
Join the club!
他们不是一般的怪物  迪恩
These are not just monsters, Dean.
他们是利维坦
They're leviathan.
他们想要我的命
I have a price on my head,
我必须先他们一步  才能
and I've been trying to stay one step ahead of them, to --
才能让他们远离你
to keep them away from you.
这就是我逃跑的原因
That's why I ran.
你们请走吧
Just leave me, please.
那就这样吧  我们走
Sounds like a plan. Let's roll.
等等  等等
Hold on, hold on.
小卡  我们要走了
Cass, we're getting out of here.
一起回家
We're going home.
迪恩  我不能
Dean, I can't.
你可以的  本尼  告诉他
You can. Benny, tell him.
炼狱有一个出口
Purgatory has an escape hatch,
对天使管不管用我就不知道了
but I got no idea if it's angel-friendly.
我们会有办法的
We'll figure it out.
小卡  伙计  我需要你
Cass, buddy, I need you.
迪恩
Dean...
如果利维坦想攻击我们  就让他们来吧
And if leviathan want to take a shot at us, let them.
我们杀过一次这些贱人
We ganked those bitches once before.
我们可以再来一次
We can do it again.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我跟你说明白
Let me bottom-line it for you.
没有你我不走
I'm not leaving here without you.
懂了吗
Understand?
我懂
I understand.
女士们  先生们  其他生灵们
Ladies, gentlemen, and...other,
欢迎光临千载难逢的盛典
Welcome to this once-in-a-lifetime event.
萨曼德里奥
Samandriel.
来探访贫民窟了
Slumming it, are we?
魔法器具与炼金秘籍的第一拍卖场
The first name in magical and alchemical esoterica.
我们的拍价不匪
Our prices may be high,
但是奇货自有天价
but our quality is unmatched,
而且信用毋庸置疑
and we stand by our products.
你们为什么对一块泥巴那么上心啊
Don't know why you're so keen on that hunk of dirt.
不过是教你们如何干掉几个恶魔
So it tells you how to blast back a few demons?
我再造就是
I'll just make more.
我的黑眼手下你们杀不干净的  萨曼莎
Can't get rid of all of my black-eyed boys, Samantha.
走着瞧
Yeah, we'll see.
备用计划有多少资金支持
All right. So, how much we got for plan "B"?
我们有伪造的信用卡
Uh, well, we got our hacked credit cards,
两千美元  还有超市会员卡
$2,000, and a, uh, Costco membership.
第一件拍品  赫斯珀勒斯的护身符
Our first item, the amulet of hesperus.
起拍价是  三吨矮人黄金
Let's start the bidding with, um, three tons of dwarven gold?
这位女士
Ah. This lady.
现价三吨  有人出四吨吗
I have three. Do I have, uh, four?
四吨  这位先生
Ah. Four, gentlemen here.
现价四吨  有人出五吨吗  五吨
Four. Going for five. Five?
这位女士出五吨
Five to this lady.
启用第二备用计划
Plan "C"?
必须的
Big time.
还有出价吗  还有吗
Any other bids? Any other bids?
我去下洗手间
I'm gonna use the restroom.
成交
Sold.
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
这里不是男厕所
This isn't the men's room.
好吧
Okay.
下一件拍品  托尔的武器  雷神之锤
Our next item up for bid, the hammer of Thor, Mjoelnir.
霜巨人伊米尔的指骨
A finger bone from the frost giant Ymir.
指骨  外加
Uh...the bone and, uh,
八分之五个处女
5/8 of a virgin.
成交
Ah. Sold.
第二备用计划失败
Plan "C" tanked.
不如试试白痴计划
Maybe you should try plan "D" for dumbass.
下一件  神之语  上帝之语
Our next lot, the word of God, capital "G" --
非常古老  非常珍贵
Very old, very rare.
三十亿美元
$3 billion.
《蒙娜丽莎》
The "Mona Lisa."
《蒙娜丽莎》真品  无上装的那版
The real "Mona Lisa," where she's topless.
梵蒂冈城
Vatican City.
阿拉斯加
Alaska.
佩林和绝路桥吗  敬谢不敏
Palin and a bridge to nowhere? No, thanks.
好吧  月球
All right. The moon.
你出月球
You're bidding the moon?
对呀  是地狱属地
Yeah. Claimed it for hell.
你以为巴斯光年是怎么进太空的
Think a man named Buzz gets to go into space without making a deal?
先生们  抱歉
Ah. I'm sorry, gentlemen.
还没人达到我们的预期底价
It seems that our reserve price has not been met.
为了刺激诸位的竞价热情
So in order to stimulate the bidding,
我们增添一件拍品
we're going to add an item to this lot --
凯文・谭  上帝的先知
Kevin Tran, prophet of the lord.
不
No!
谭先生是世上唯一能够解读神之语的人
Mr. Tran is the only person on earth who can read this tablet,
这一对拍品珠联璧合
which makes them a perfect matching set.
你是买不起的
So out of your league.
有人出价吗
So, do I hear a bid of --
不  停下
No, stop!
你们要什么我都给
I'll give you whatever you want.
我的养老金  还有房子
I have a 401K, my house.
非常慷慨  谭夫人
Good effort, Ms. Tran,
只怕价钱远不是你能力所及
but I'm afraid this is a little out of your price range.
我的灵魂
My soul.
妈  不要
Mom, don't!
我出我的灵魂
I bid my soul!
你确定吗  这可是重大决定
Are you sure? That's a big move.
有趣
Interesting.
如果你们要的是灵魂
If it's souls that you're after,
我可以给你们一百万
I can give you a million souls.
飞行小子  你不加入吗
Hey, flyboy, are you gonna get in on this?
我们守护天堂里的灵魂  不能拿来交易
We guard the souls in heaven. We don't horse-trade them.
那么我们成交
So we have a deal.
关键不在于数量
It's not about the quantity, chief.
而在于牺牲
It's about the sacrifice.
这位女士的灵魂是她最宝贵的东西
This little lady's soul is the most valuable thing she has.
是她的一切
It's everything.
你愿意付出一切吗  克劳力先生
Are you willing to offer everything, Mr. Crowley?
要快哦
Tick-tock.
好吧  你赢了
Fine. You win.
我出
I bid...
我的灵魂
my own soul!
克劳力先生  你没有灵魂
Mr. Crowley, you don't have a soul.
恭喜你  甜心
Congrats, sweetheart.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
失去灵魂
Losing my soul
会疼吗
is it going to hurt?
有可能
Probably.
我会死吗
Will I die?
不  只会生不如死
No. You'll just wish you were dead.
好吧
Okay.
时候到了
It's time.
你没事吧
You all right?
没事
Yeah.
让我单独待会儿行吗
Can I -- can I just have a minute?
迪恩  这可糟透了
Dean, this sucks.
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
我们要永远关上地狱之门
We're about to close the gates of hell forever.
要我说  是我们占便宜了
If you ask me, we got off cheap.
抱歉  女士
Excuse me, Miss.
你好  我叫萨...阿尔菲
Hi. My name is Sam-- Alfie.
我是天使
I'm an angel.
你在香肠店工作
Who works at Wiener Hut?
不  这是...这不重要
No. This is, uh -- it doesn't matter.
你刚刚的所作所为真的很惊人
Uh, what you did in here was amazing,
我想告诉你
and I want you to know that
我和我的朋友可以保护你儿子
my friends and I can protect your son.
温彻斯特兄弟很特别
The Winchesters are exceptional men,
但是  他们也只是人类
but...they're just men.
如果凯文和我们在一起
If Kevin comes with us --
不  不
Oh, no, no.
上一次  天使想要帮助我儿子
The last time that angels tried to help my son,
却死在我面前
I watched them die,
而凯文失踪了近一年
and Kevin went missing for a year.
所以  无意冒犯
So, no offense,
但是这次我要相信他们
but I'm gonna take my chances with them.
雷神之锤  我好想你
Mjoelnir, I've missed you.
那孩子在哪
Where's the kid?
你打算怎么处理她的灵魂
What are you gonna do with her soul?
想怎么就怎样
Whatever I want.
也许会卖了它
I might sell it,
也许会像对待其他珍贵物品一样  藏起来
or maybe I'll just tuck it away with my other precious objects,
夜里用来取暖
let them keep me warm at night.
亲爱的  就等你了
Whenever you're ready, dear.
等等
Wait!
你们好  孩子们
Hello, boys.
克劳力
Crowley.
不  不可能  有屏障法术
No. You can't. My warding spells.
你的小妞告诉了我几处漏洞
Your girl Friday showed me a few loopholes.
无意冒犯  但是这次我要相信他们
No offense, but I'm going to take my chances with them.
那么做
Now, that...
是非常非常愚蠢的
...was very, very stupid!
只不过花了我在南太平洋的一座岛屿
And all it cost me was an island in the south Pacific.
我爱死交易了
I love a bargain.
虽然法力有限  但是也够了
Can't do all my tricks, but I can do enough.
从她身上滚出来
Get out of her!
要是每次有人对我这么大叫
If I had a nickel for every time
我就能获得五美分的话
someone screamed that at me...
克劳力  在挖掘你女性化的一面吗
Getting in touch with your feminine side, huh, Crowley?
差不多吧
Something like that.
去抓住他
Well, come and get him.
二取一也不错
One out of two ain't bad.
看好那孩子
Watch the kid!
凯文  别去  让迪恩去解决
Kevin, don't! Let Dean take care of it.
萨姆  闪开
Sam, move!
不要
Don't!
你知道有什么是比一座私人岛屿更好吗
You know what's better than one private island?
两座私人岛屿
Two private islands.
好了  还给我
Okay. Give it back.
还给我
Give it back.
你从哪弄来的八分之五的处女
Where'd you get the 5/8 of a virgin?
不要
Oh, no.
妈妈
Mom!
真令人兴奋啊
Well, that was exciting.
没了这个
Good luck closing the gates to hell...
看你们怎么关上地狱之门
...without this.
你妈妈脑海中念头可真让人吃惊
Surprising what mommy dearest has rattling around in her head.
想知道你亲生父亲是谁吗
Want to know who your real father is?
-令人震惊  -克劳力
- Scandalous. - Crowley!
凯文  我知道我们不是伙伴
I know we're not mates, Kevin,
但送你一个字的建议  跑
but one word of advice -- run.
跑得远远的  越快越好
Run far and run fast.
因为温彻斯特兄弟
'Cause the Winchesters --
他们习惯利用别人
well, they have a habit of using people up
然后看着他们惨死
and watching them die bloody.
再见了
Toodles.
她说什么了吗
Has she said anything?
听着  凯文  你妈妈所经历的
Listen, Kev, what your mom went through --
是地狱
It's hell.
相信我  我了解
Trust me, I know.
但她似乎很坚强  她会振作起来的
But she seems tough. She'll pull it together.
你想杀死她
You tried to kill her.
孩子  在这世上...
Kid, in this life --
闭嘴
Shut up!
我再也不想听你那一套了
I don't want to hear any more of your crappy speeches.
我只想单独和我妈说会儿话
I just want to talk to my mom alone.
好的
Sure.
五分钟
Five minutes.
妈
Mom...
迪恩  刚刚你真的是要
Dean, were you really going to, uh...
什么  撕开虎妈的喉咙吗
What? Slit soccer mom's throat?
是的  我那么做就对了
Yeah, I was. I wish I had.
迪恩
Dean --
萨姆  那是克劳力
It was Crowley, Sam.
不管他在哪个肉身里
No matter what meat suit he's in,
我都应该捅死他
I should have knifed him.
是的  这样做很不好  我也会恨我自己
I mean, yeah, it would have sucked, and I would have hated myself,
但是只是又添一个噩梦而已  不是吗
but what's one more nightmare, right?
你有没有觉得那里有点太安静了
It seem a little quiet in there to you?
凯文
Kevin?
Kevin!
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me!
看这里
Hey.
什么
What?
上面说什么
What's it say?
他们逃走了  劝我们别去追
Uh, that they bolted, that we shouldn't come looking,
既然我们没了石碑
and since we lost the tablet,
凯文觉得我们不需要他了
Kevin figures we don't need him.
没错  但是克劳力有石碑
Yeah, but Crowley still does.
那孩子想什么呢
What's that kid thinking?!
他觉得对我没用处的人都会死
He thinks people I don't need anymore they end up dead.
迪恩  那...那不是真的  你知道的
Dean, that -- that -- that's not true. You know that.
迪恩  迪恩
Dean! Dean!
迪恩
Dean!